How do I use Presenter view without a projector or second monitor?

Use Win+P keyboard shortcut to bring up the (Connect to projector) window.
    Click "Extend" option. This will bring the second display output "alive" although no monitor/projector is connected there.
    In PowerPoint, open your presentation and click "Slide Show" | "Set Up Show" item
Select the slide show to display on Monitor 2 and check the "Show Presenter View" box, click OK.
    Now start slide show. The presenter view will be on your laptop while PowerPoint is gladly thinking that the slide show is being shown on the second monitor.
